[{"Response":"10 - Completely worthwhile","Percentage of respondents":25.2,"Question":"Overall, to what extent do you feel the things you do in your life are worthwhile?","Year":2022},{"Response":"9","Percentage of respondents":11.3,"Question":"Overall, to what extent do you feel the things you do in your life are worthwhile?","Year":2022},{"Response":"8","Percentage of respondents":27.6,"Question":"Overall, to what extent do you feel the things you do in your life are worthwhile?","Year":2022},{"Response":"7","Percentage of respondents":16.5,"Question":"Overall, to what extent do you feel the things you do in your life are worthwhile?","Year":2022},{"Response":"6","Percentage of respondents":5.9,"Question":"Overall, to what extent do you feel the things you do in your life are worthwhile?","Year":2022},{"Response":"5","Percentage of respondents":5.6,"Question":"Overall, to what extent do you feel the things you do in your life are worthwhile?","Year":2022},{"Response":"4","Percentage of respondents":1.3,"Question":"Overall, to what extent do you feel the things you do in your life are worthwhile?","Year":2022},{"Response":"3","Percentage of respondents":1.3,"Question":"Overall, to what extent do you feel the things you do in your life are worthwhile?","Year":2022},{"Response":"2","Percentage of respondents":0.6,"Question":"Overall, to what extent do you feel the things you do in your life are worthwhile?","Year":2022},{"Response":"1","Percentage of respondents":0.3,"Question":"Overall, to what extent do you feel the things you do in your life are worthwhile?","Year":2022},{"Response":"0 - Not at all worthwhile","Percentage of respondents":0.7,"Question":"Overall, to what extent do you feel the things you do in your life are worthwhile?","Year":2022},{"Response":"10 - Completely anxious ","Percentage of respondents":4.2,"Question":"How anxious did you feel yesterday?","Year":2022},{"Response":"9 ","Percentage of respondents":2.9,"Question":"How anxious did you feel yesterday?","Year":2022},{"Response":"8 ","Percentage of respondents":7.2,"Question":"How anxious did you feel yesterday?","Year":2022},{"Response":"7 ","Percentage of respondents":10.2,"Question":"How anxious did you feel yesterday?","Year":2022},{"Response":"6 ","Percentage of respondents":8.4,"Question":"How anxious did you feel yesterday?","Year":2022},{"Response":"5 ","Percentage of respondents":11.1,"Question":"How anxious did you feel yesterday?","Year":2022},{"Response":"4 ","Percentage of respondents":5.6,"Question":"How anxious did you feel yesterday?","Year":2022},{"Response":"3 ","Percentage of respondents":7.8,"Question":"How anxious did you feel yesterday?","Year":2022},{"Response":"2 ","Percentage of respondents":9.8,"Question":"How anxious did you feel yesterday?","Year":2022},{"Response":"1 ","Percentage of respondents":6.0,"Question":"How anxious did you feel yesterday?","Year":2022},{"Response":"0 - Not at all anxious ","Percentage of respondents":23.0,"Question":"How anxious did you feel yesterday?","Year":2022}]